<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <!-- TODO: ADD MORE AND TRANSLATE MOTIVATIONAL PHRASES -->
    <string-array name="motivational">
        <item id="1">You can find the sources to these facts in the settings!</item>
        <item id="1">Water helps to maximize physical performance.</item>
        <item id="1">Hydration has a major effect on energy levels and brain function.</item>
        <item id="1">Drinking water may help to prevent and treat headaches.</item>
        <item id="1">Drinking more water may help relieve constipation.</item>
        <item id="1">Drinking water may help treat kidney stones.</item>
        <item id="1">Water helps prevent hangovers.</item>
        <item id="1">Drinking more water can help with weight loss.</item>
        <item id="2">A deficiency in Vitamin D can cause rickets.</item>
        <item id="2">A combination of calcium, vitamin D, vitamin K, magnesium, and phosphorus protects your bones against fractures.</item>
        <item id="2">Several B vitamins are key components of certain coenzymes that help release energy from food.</item>
        <item id="2">Bone formation would be impossible without vitamins A, D, and K.</item>
        <item id="2">Vitamin A helps keep cells healthy and protects your vision.</item>
        <item id="3">Sugary drinks are the most fattening product in the modern diet.</item>
        <item id="4">Eating bats might be a major public health risk.</item>
        <item id="5">Use of the artificial sweetener aspartame has been linked to neurological and behavioral disturbances in sensitive individuals.</item>
        <item id="6">The mushroom is the only non-animal natural source of vitamin D.</item>
        <item id="7">Major brain damage from alcohol can be prevented by proper nutrition and is not directly caused by alcohol itself.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="motivational_source">
        <item id="1">https://www.healthline.com/nutrition/7-health-benefits-of-water#section7</item>
        <item id="2">https://www.helpguide.org/harvard/vitamins-and-minerals.htm</item>
        <item id="3">https://www.healthline.com/nutrition/20-nutrition-facts-that-should-be-common-sense#section16</item>
        <item id="4">https://www.sciencedaily.com/releases/2020/03/200317175442.htm</item>
        <item id="5">https://nutritionfacts.org/video/aspartame-and-the-brain/</item>
        <item id="6">https://www.justvitamins.co.uk/blog/some-interesting-food-facts/</item>
        <item id="7">https://factrepublic.com/40-interesting-nutrition-facts-you-have-to-know/</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>